A Guide to the American Public Transportation Association Collection
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
American Public Transportation Association Collection
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
APTA0001
90 cubic feet (145 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is without restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
The American Public Transit Association (APTA) was created in 1974 with the merging of two major American transit-related organizations, the American Transit Association (ATA) and the Institute for Rapid Transit (IRT). Both organizations trace their histories back decades before this date. The ATA, which originated in 1932, specialized in issues dealing with motor busses and trolley coaches and other motorized transit vehicles. The IRT, organized in 1961, specialized in electric railways and other rapid-transit sources. In January 2000 the name of the organization was changed to the American Public Transportation Association. Today APTA is a leading participant in research and legislation regarding the American transportation industry and issues relating to it.
Scope and Content Information
Collection contains subject-arranged materials pertaining particularly to the American Public Transit Association. Also included are materials from both the American Transit Association (ATA)and the Institute for Rapid Transit (IRT). Types of materials in the collection include: memoranda, correspondence, reports, legislative information, industry-related information (such as brochures and technical reports), and membership information.
Arrangement
Arrangement for the APTA Collection is by subject/topic.
Contents List
- American Public Transportation Association Collection
  - Operating Association Executive Minutes (Box Box 1)
  - Operating Association Executive Minutes (Box Box 1)
  - Operating Association Executive Minutes (Box Box 1)
  - Operating Association Executive Minutes (Box Box 1)
  - Operation Association Executive Minutes (Box Box 1)
  - PERMANENT NOMINATIONS (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER 1970-1971 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER 10-8-71 MEETING (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 1/26/70 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION GENERAL (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER MEETING 6/30/1970 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER 9/20/1970 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 1/29/1970 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 2/19/69 (Box Box 1)
  - ENTERTAINMENT COMMITTEE 4/9/69 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 2/23/70 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 2/20/69 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION 8/8/69 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER MEETING 2/14/72 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBERS COMMITTEE MEETING 5/22/72 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER 1/27/72 (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION (Box Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATE MEMBER DIVISION (Box Box 1)
  - Associate Member Committee (860) 1974-1975 (Box Box 1)
  - Motor Coach Interchange Materials (Box Box 1)
  - Substitute Materials (Box Box 1)
  - 873.1 Comm. on Materials Management (Box Box 1)
  - 873.1 Substitute Materials (Box Box 1)
  - Motor Coach Substitute Materials (Box Box 1)
  - 1969-70 Roster (Box Box 1)
  - Minutes of November 169 Comm. Meeting (Box Box 1)
  - Purchases and Materials Management (Box Box 1)
  - Legal Opinions-Loss and Damages (Box Box 1)
  - Gift for McCaul (Box Box 1)
  - Officers Committees of the Purchases and Materials Management Division 1968 and 1969 (Box Box 1)
  - 1970 Purchase and Materials Management Administrative Committee (Box Box 1)
  - READING FILE-TSG August 5, 1981 Dec.4-30 1981 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE-TSG August 5, 1981 Dec 4-30 1981 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE-TSG January 1982 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE-TSG January 1982 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE FOR TSG October 1982 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE FOR TSG October 1982 (Box Box 2)
  - READING FILE FOR TSG October 1982 (Box Box 2)
  - BATTERY ENERGY STORAGE (Box Box 2)
  - BATTERY ENERGY STORAGE (Box Box 2)
  - BATTERY ENERGY STORAGE (Box Box 2)
  - NYSERDA/DOE/NYCTA BATTERY ENERGY STORAGE PLANT (Box Box 3)
  - REPORT-BATTERY STORAGE A LOAD MANAGEMENT OPTION (Box Box 3)
  - TECHNICAL AND RESEARCH SERVICES (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE FEB-MAR 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG FEB-MAR 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG April 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG MAY 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG MAY 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - ENERGY STORAGE PROJECT N.Y. ENERGY (Box Box 3)
  - ENERGY STORAGE PROJECT N.Y. ENERGY (Box Box 3)
  - TSG READING FILE November 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE FOR TSG December 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG June 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG August 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG September 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG September 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG July 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG June 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG June 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - READING FILE-TSG June 1982 (Box Box 3)
  - 075.232 TRUCK RULES AND REGULATIONS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.204 MOTOR VEHICLE EQUIPMENT REGULATIONS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.402.1 LICENSE PLATES (Box Box 4)
  - 075.203.1 REGROOVED TIRES (Box Box 4)
  - 075.203.1 REGROOVED TIRES (Box Box 4)
  - 075.203.1 REGROOVED TIRES (Box Box 4)
  - 075.202 DRIVER LICENSES REQUIREMENTS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.202 DRIVER LICENSES REQUIREMENTS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.202 DRIVER LICENSES REQUIREMENTS (Box Box 4)
  - DRAFT REPORTS CARPOOLING (Box Box 4)
  - STATE OF MICHIGAN-Vehicle Code-1949 (Box Box 4)
  - 075.201 SIZES & WEIGHTS-RESTRICTIONS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.201 SIZES & WEIGHTS-RESTRICTIONS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.21 COMMON CARRIER REGULATIONS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.23 COMMISSION POWERS OVER MOTOR CARRIERS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.203 TIRE RESTRICTIONS-RETREADS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.1 SAFETY-PRIVATE CARRIERS (Box Box 4)
  - 075.59 TAXICABS-LOCAL INFORMATION (Box Box 4)
  - 075.61 ICC RULING ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 VIRGINIA (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 WASHINGTON (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 WEST VIRGINIA (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 WISCONSIN (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 WYOMING (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 WYOMING (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 MOTOR BUS LAWS-CANADA (Box Box 4)
  - 075.2 PENNSYLVANIA (Box Box 4)
  - TRUST FUND HEARINGS 3/11/70 (Box Box 5)
  - STATEMENTS/MAPS (Box Box 5)
  - 814.8 LEGISLATIVE COMM 1972-1973 (Box Box 5)
  - TRUST FUND HEARING 3/04/70 (Box Box 5)
  - 814.8 TRUST FUND HEARINGS 3/5/20 (Box Box 5)
  - 077.241 REPORTS OPERATION DATA;REGS BY REGULATORY BOARD (Box Box 5)
  - 077.252 COMMISSION AUDIT OF ACCOUNTS (Box Box 5)
  - 077.23 ACCOUNTS-REGULATIONS (Box Box 5)
  - 077.22 CAPITALIZATION REGULATION (Box Box 5)
  - 077.26 REGULATIONS OF SERVICE (Box Box 5)
  - 077.253 RATES, PAST EARNINGS OR LOSSES RULINGS (Box Box 5)
  - 077.251 JUST AND REASONABLE CHARGE (Box Box 5)
  - COMMISSIONS (Box Box 5)
  - LIBRARY STUDY AND EVALUATION OF URBAN MASS TRANSPORTATION REGULATION AND REGULATORY BODIES (Box Box 5)
  - 075 MUNICIPAL FRANCHISING AND REGULATION (Box Box 5)
  - INTERSTATE COMMERCE COMMISSION GENERAL RULES OF PRACTICE (Box Box 5)
  - 074.32 SPECIAL INQUIRY FUEL TAX EXEMPTION (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 MISSISIPPI (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 NEW HAMPSHIRE (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 NEW JERSEY (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 OHIO (Box Box 5)
  - 0.75.2 NEW YORK (Box Box 5)
  - 0.75.1 SAFETY MECHANICAL REGULATIONS (Box Box 5)
  - 0.75.12 HOUGOMOI (Box Box 5)
  - 075.102 LICENCE REQUIREMENTS (Box Box 5)
  - 075.12 ICC REGULATIONS OF MOTOR TRUCKS (Box Box 5)
  - 075.12 ICC RAIL (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 MOTOR VEHICLE LAWS-GENERAL (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 CALIFORNIA (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 DELAWARE (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 CONNECTICUT (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 ILLINOIS (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 INDIANA (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 KENTUCKY (Box Box 5)
  - 075.2 MASSACHUSETTS (Box Box 5)
  - 075.233 REGS OF SCHOOL CHARTER BUS SERVICE DEC'58 (Box Box 5)
  - 075.233 REGS OF SCHOOL CHARTER BUS SERVICE December 1958 (Box Box 5)
  - 075.233 NEW YORKS WORLDS FAIR-CHARTER BUS REGS-'39 (Box Box 5)
  - 075.233 CHARTER BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 5)
  - TIRES 1967 (Box Box 6)
  - TIRES 1967 (Box Box 6)
  - 900 LOS ANGELES (Box Box 6)
  - 900 MUNI (Box Box 6)
  - 900 MUNI (Box Box 6)
  - 900 ILL-CHICAGO-GENERAL (Box Box 6)
  - 900.01 GENERAL/MISCELLANEOUS (Box Box 6)
  - 824.73 MODERN MACHINE ACCOUNTING (Box Box 6)
  - 824.73 PUNCH CARD ACCOUNTING (Box Box 6)
  - 824.82 MANUAL OF PAY ROLL PROCEDURE April-1949 (Box Box 6)
  - 824.82 MODERN DEVELOPMENTS IN PAY ROLL PROCEDURE (Box Box 6)
  - TAX ADVISORY COMMITTEE (Box Box 6)
  - 814.95 PRINCIPLES OF RATE REGULATION (Box Box 6)
  - 814.816 SMALL BUS SPECIFICATIONS (Box Box 6)
  - 824.21 STANDARD CLASSIFICATION OF ACCOUNTS (Box Box 6)
  - 824.214 TROLLEY COACH ACCOUNTING (Box Box 6)
  - 824.28 PRESERVATION OF RECORDS (Box Box 6)
  - 824.51 INTERNAL CONTROL (Box Box 6)
  - 824.72 COMMITTEE ON ACCOUNTING PRACTICES (Box Box 6)
  - 824.721 SUBCOMMITTEE ON NON-UTILITY ACTIVITIES (Box Box 6)
  - 635.6 NEWSPAPERS (Box Box 6)
  - 640.03 MOTOR BUSES (Box Box 6)
  - 814.91 COMMITTEE ON ADVERTISING REVENUE (Box Box 6)
  - 814.816 BUS DESIGN REPORT (Box Box 6)
  - 814.816 BUS DESIGN REPORT (Box Box 6)
  - KEENE CORP-JOHNSON Fare Boxes (Box Box 6)
  - 618.38 SHORTAGES AND AVERAGES (Box Box 6)
  - 814.817 TRUCK REPAIR AND SERVICE DIRECTORY (Box Box 6)
  - 618.39 LOCKED FARE BOXES (Box Box 6)
  - TRUST FUND HEARING MARCH 10, 1970 (Box Box 7)
  - TRUST FUND HEARING MARCH 10, 1970 (Box Box 7)
  - MASS TRANSIT HEARINGS (Report of Proceedings) (Box Box 7)
  - MASS TRANSIT HEARINGS (Report of Proceedings) (Box Box 7)
  - MASS TRANSIT HEARINGS (Report of Proceedings) (Box Box 7)
  - SURFACE TRANSPORTATION ACT 1972 (Box Box 7)
  - DOT 1976 APPROPRIATIONS-'77 (Box Box 7)
  - ATA IRT LEGISLATIVE COMMITTEE (Box Box 7)
  - ATA IRT LEGISLATIVE COMMITTEE (Box Box 7)
  - TRANSIT TRUST FUND-GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 7)
  - RESPONSES TO HR 16261 FROM MEMBERS (Box Box 7)
  - TESTIMONY MAY 18, 1970 (Box Box 7)
  - MASS TRANSIT HEARING [Vol 5](Report of Proceedings) (Box Box 7)
  - SEMINAR ON 3154 12/15/70 (Box Box 7)
  - PRESIDENTS STATEMENTS ON PUBLIC TRANSPORT 8/7/69 (Box Box 7)
  - 814.8 STATEMENT, TESTIMONY, BILLS (Box Box 7)
  - 874 TRANSIT LEGISLATION (Box Box 7)
  - COMMITTEE ON INTERSTATE AND FOREIGN COMMERCE v.s. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES (Box Box 7)
  - SENATE SUBSIDY BILL (Box Box 7)
  - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD/ARTICLE AMENDMENT/LEGISLATION (Box Box 7)
  - 900 D.C. General (Box Box 8)
  - 900 D.C. General (Box Box 8)
  - Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission (Box Box 8)
  - 900 U.S. Possessions (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PITTSBURGH (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PITTSBURGH (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PHILADELPHIA (Box Box 8)
  - 900 D.C. Transit (Box Box 8)
  - 900 National Capital Transportation Agency (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Wisconsin General (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Tennessee (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Washington (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Texas (Box Box 8)
  - 900.001 Discontinued Electric (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Seattle World's Fair (Box Box 8)
  - 900 D.C. General (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Ohio (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Illinois - General (Box Box 8)
  - 900 P.A. ALLEGHENY COUNTY PORT AUTHORITY (PAAC) (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PHILADELPHIA (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PITTSBURGH (Box Box 8)
  - 900 PITTSBURGH (Box Box 8)
  - 900 Pennsylvania (Box Box 8)
  - DIRECTORY, REPORTS & MAPS (Box Box 8)
  - DIRECTORY, REPORTS & MAPS (Box Box 8)
  - 900.1 MISSOURI (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 MONTANA (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 NEBRASKA (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 NEVADA (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 NEW HAMPSHIRE (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 MASSACHUSETTS (Box Box 9)
  - BUS COMPANY FAILURES - Meeting (Box Box 9)
  - Michigan Public Transportation Directory (Box Box 9)
  - Plan of Reorganization (Box Box 9)
  - Central Automated Transit System (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Massachusetts (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Massachusetts (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Alberguergue (Box Box 9)
  - Readjustment of Transaction Agreement May 31, 1935 (Box Box 9)
  - Transcript of Testimony (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Fifth Avenue (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Long Island Railroad Company (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 Long Island Railroad Company (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 MICHIGAN (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 MICHIGAN (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 NEW JERSEY (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 NEW JERSEY (Box Box 9)
  - 900.013 NEW YORK (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 TWIN CITY/MINNESOTA (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 TWIN CITY/MINNESOTA (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 TWIN CITY/MINNESOTA (Box Box 9)
  - 900.01 MISSISSIPPI (GENERAL) (Box Box 9)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY AND MAINTENANCE (Box Box 10)
  - Joint Trackwork Electrical Design Guidelines (Box Box 10)
  - 840 Rehabilitation and Modernization Task Force (Box Box 10)
  - State Regulations on Trolley Cars (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 APTA SYSTEM SAFETY COMM. (Box Box 10)
  - 840 Stars (Box Box 10)
  - CAR EQUIPMENT (Box Box 10)
  - CAR EQUIPMENT (Box Box 10)
  - NFPA STANDARD ON FIXED GUIDE TRANSIT-REPORT (Box Box 10)
  - NFPA STANDARD ON FIXED GUIDE TRANSIT-REPORT (Box Box 10)
  - 900 NYC INTERBOUROUGH (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NEW YORK STATEN ISLAND (Box Box 11)
  - 900 MASSACHUSETTS GEN (Box Box 11)
  - 900 MASSACHUSETTS GEN. (Box Box 11)
  - 900 6th AVENUE (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NYC TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NYC TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NEW YORK CENTRAL (Box Box 11)
  - 900 3rd AVENUE (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NYC INDEPENDENT (Box Box 11)
  - 900 REPORTS (Box Box 11)
  - 900 REPORTS (Box Box 11)
  - 900 REPORTS (Box Box 11)
  - STATISTICAL GUIDE FOR NEW YORK CITY (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NYC LONG ISLAND (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NYC LONG ISLAND (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NEW YORK TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NEW YORK TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 11)
  - 900 NEW YORK TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 11)
  - 900.01 COLUMBUS OH. (Box Box 12)
  - IDEA 27th ANNUAL CONFERENCE (Box Box 12)
  - APTA 200 CONFERENCES, SEMINARS/WEEKLY MAGAZINE (Box Box 12)
  - 900.1 GREATER CLEVELAND-Regional Transit Authority (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 SEPTA (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 SEPTA (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 SEPTA (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 ALLEN COUNTY REG. TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 MIAMI VALLEY REGIONAL TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 CHARLOTTE TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 TOLEDO AREA REGIONAL TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 12)
  - DUKE POWER COMPANY (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 NORTH DAKOTA (GENERAL) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 YOUNGSTOWN, OHIO (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 METRO REGIONAL TRANSIT AUTH (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 QUENN CITY METRO (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 OHIO (GENERAL) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 OH (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 OKLAHOMA (GENERAL) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 PORTLAND, OREGON (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 OREGON (GENERAL) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 PITTSBURGH, PA (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 PENNSYLVANIA (GENERAL CON'T) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 FIFTH AVENUE - Surface Transit Condemnation (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 FIFTH AVENUE - Surface Transit Condemnation (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 FIFTH AVE ROBERTS CROSS EXAMINATION (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 NIAGARA FRONTIER TRANSIT METRO SYSTEM (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 ROCHESTER-GENESEE REGIONAL TRANSPORTATION AUTHORITY (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 SCHENECTADY (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 REGIONAL TRANSIT SERVICE (ROCHESTER) (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 UNITED TRACTION, N.Y. (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 SYRACUSE (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 INTERNATIONAL RAILWAY CO. (Box Box 12)
  - 900.01 INTERNATIONAL RAILWAY CO. (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 INTL. RAILWAY CO. - Proposal of Plan of Reorganization (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 OHIO (GENERAL) (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NORTH CAROLINA (GENERAL) (Box Box 13)
  - CENTRAL OHIO TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 CENTRAL OHIO TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 CENTRAL OHIO TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NASSAU COUNTY, N.Y. (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 FIFTH AVENUE N.Y. (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NYC GREEN BUS LINES (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NYC STATEN ISLAND (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK CITY TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK CITY TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 NYC SURFACE TRANSIT INC. (Box Box 13)
  - 900.01 SYRACUSE TRANSIT CORP. N.Y. (Box Box 13)
  - REPORT OF THE APTA TRACTION MOTOR PERFORMANCE TASK FORCE (Box Box 14)
  - AMERICAN TRANSIT ASSOCIATION SCHEDULE COMMITTEE (Box Box 14)
  - EXPRESSWAY BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 14)
  - APPENDIX TO APTA PETITION (Box Box 14)
  - 1983 Reports of Transaction Motor Performance Task Force (Box Box 14)
  - ASAE Evaluation Report (Box Box 14)
  - SEMAPHORES ON VEHICLE USED IN SCHOOL BUS SERVICE June 3rd, 1964 (Box Box 14)
  - OPERATORS WAGE CHANGES (Box Box 14)
  - OPERATORS' WAGE CHANGES (Box Box 14)
  - Instructions of Operations and Trolley Coaches (Box Box 14)
  - Code#'s, Industrial Injuries, Transit Industry 1938-1956 (Box Box 14)
  - Carbon monoxide Poisoning and Exhaust Fume Elimination (Box Box 14)
  - STATISTICS OF ELECTRIC RAILWAYS OF CANADA 1943-1952 (Box Box 14)
  - STATISTICS OF ELECTRIC RAILWAYS OF CANADA 1943-1952 (Box Box 14)
  - Carbon monoxide Poisoning and Exhaust Fume Elimination (Box Box 14)
  - 900.01 ALASKA (GENERAL) (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 ALABAMA (GENERAL) (Box Box 15)
  - ROUTE MAPS 10/25/65 (Box Box 15)
  - 900 UNITED STATES-GENERAL (Box Box 15)
  - CITY EXHIBITS (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 NEW JERSEY/NEW YORK/ (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 COMPARISONS OF TNJ AND OTHER LARGE BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 TACOMA TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 TACOMA TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 MASSACHUSETTS (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 MASSACHUSETTS (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 NEW MEXICO (GENERAL) (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 INDEPENDENT (Box Box 15)
  - Feasibility and Desirability of Privately Provided Transit Service 900.01 TECHNICAL REPORT (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK Miscellaneous Clippings (Box Box 15)
  - 900 NEW YORK STATE (Box Box 15)
  - 900 MARYLAND-BALTIMORE (Box Box 15)
  - 900.01 (Box Box 15)
  - N.E. GROUP (Box Box 15)
  - LOUISINA (Box Box 15)
  - 900 INDIANA (Box Box 15)
  - 900 MAINE (Box Box 15)
  - Public Law 86th CONGRESS 7/14/60 (Box Box 15)
  - 900 MARYLAND BALTIMORE TRANSIT CO. (Box Box 15)
  - 900 MARYLAND BALTIMORE TRANSIT CO. (Box Box 15)
  - 900.001 Discontinued/Abandonned Railway Operations (Box Box 15)
  - REGROOVED TIRES-POSITIVE REPLIES (Box Box 16)
  - REGROOVED TIRES-POSITIVE REPLIES (Box Box 16)
  - REGROOVED TIRES-POSITIVE REPLIES (Box Box 16)
  - REGROOVED TIRES-POSITIVE REPLIES (Box Box 16)
  - REGROOVED TIRES (CANADA) 8/25/67 (Box Box 16)
  - BLS SURVEY-BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS (Box Box 16)
  - BLS SURVEY-BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS (Box Box 16)
  - BLS SURVEY-BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS (Box Box 16)
  - BLS SURVEY-BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS (Box Box 16)
  - FLSA SPECIAL REPORT OVERTIME (Box Box 16)
  - REGROOVED TIRES-NEGATIVE REPLIES 8/25/67 (Box Box 16)
  - URBAN MASS TRANSPORTATION ACT (Box Box 16)
  - URBAN MASS TRANSPORTATION ACT (Box Box 16)
  - 890 PUBLIC RELATIONS '67-'69 (Box Box 16)
  - RESTRUCTURING OF P.R. DIVISION (Box Box 16)
  - ASF-IRT-ATA JOINT COMM 893.14 P.R. POLICY COMM. (Box Box 16)
  - 884.265 PCC RAPID TRANSIT EQT. (Box Box 16)
  - 884.265 SUBCOMMITTEE ON RAPID TRANSIT CARS (Box Box 16)
  - WAGE WEEKLY 1972-1974 (Box Box 17)
  - Inquiry on Sick Leave Abuse (Box Box 17)
  - OVERTIME IN THE TRANSIT INDUSTRY (Box Box 17)
  - OVERTIME IN THE TRANSIT INDUSTRY (Box Box 17)
  - 900 OREGON (Box Box 18)
  - 900 OREGON (Box Box 18)
  - CHICAGO TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 18)
  - OREGON (Box Box 18)
  - HR 9331 (Box Box 19)
  - HR 9331 (Box Box 19)
  - HOUSING ACT (Box Box 19)
  - FINANCE (Box Box 19)
  - FINANCE (Box Box 19)
  - FINANCE (Box Box 19)
  - FINANCE (Box Box 19)
  - 814.8 (FLSA) CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) LEGISLATION, AMENDMENTS, BILLS, LAWS (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) LEGISLATION, AMENDMENT, BILLS, LAWS (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) BULLETINS, MAILINGS (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) MISC> (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) STATEMENTS TESTIMONY (Box Box 19)
  - (FLSA) VOTES (Box Box 19)
  - PERLY AMEND 4/8/70 (Box Box 19)
  - PERLY AMEND 1/8/70 (Box Box 19)
  - HR 18185 (Box Box 19)
  - RESPONSES ON H.R. 18185 (Box Box 19)
  - TESTIMONY MAY 1970 FEDERAL AID TO HGWY (Box Box 19)
  - TESTIMONY MAY 20, 1970 (Box Box 19)
  - TESTIMONY JUNE 10, 1970 (Box Box 19)
  - HR 16261 (Box Box 19)
  - SEMINAR ON 3154 12/15/70 (Box Box 19)
  - HEARINGS JANUARY 1970 (Box Box 19)
  - LEGAL (Box Box 19)
  - LEGAL (Box Box 19)
  - LEGAL (Box Box 19)
  - URBAN MOTOR COACH DESIGN OBJECTIVES 4/10/58 (Box Box 20)
  - THE BUS OF THE FUTURE (Box Box 20)
  - 619.4 SAN FRANCISCO RAILWAY (Box Box 20)
  - 620 EXPRESS AND FREIGHT (Box Box 20)
  - 620.08 AIRSHIPPING (Box Box 20)
  - 618.4 FAREBOXES (Box Box 20)
  - 618.4 FARE BOXES (Box Box 20)
  - 618.22 COUNTERFEIT TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.26 COUNTERFEIT DETECTION (Box Box 20)
  - 618.27 TICKETS OR TOKENS VOIDED BY CHANGE IN RATES (Box Box 20)
  - 619.3 FARES, FERRY (Box Box 20)
  - 618.31 METHODS OF CHECKING FARES (Box Box 20)
  - 618.221 FOREIGN TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.311 OPERATORS REPORTS (Box Box 20)
  - SHORTAGES AND OVERAGES (Box Box 20)
  - 620.161 CONTAINER SYSTEM (Box Box 20)
  - 620.23 MOTOR TRUCKS (Box Box 20)
  - 630.03 MOTOR BUS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.43 MACHINES FOR MAKING CHANGE (Box Box 20)
  - 618.43 CHANGE MAKING MACHINES (Box Box 20)
  - 618.45 TICKETS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.491 TOLL COLLECTION MACHINES 6/8/49 (Box Box 20)
  - 618.5 HAND COLLECTION (Box Box 20)
  - 618.601 TOKEN ACCOUNTING PROCEDURE (Box Box 20)
  - 618.6 ACCOUNTING IN FARE COLLECTION (Box Box 20)
  - 618.61 TICKET AND COIN COUNTING (Box Box 20)
  - 618.63 ACCOUNTING FOR UNREDEENED TICKETS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.131.4 GOVT. AND LARGE CO. PURCHASE OF TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.131 TOKEN HOLDERS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.133 TOKEN ISSUING MACHINES (Box Box 20)
  - 618.171 FARE COLLECT ON ZONE SYSTEM (Box Box 20)
  - 618.18 CREDIT SYSTEM OF FAIR PAYMENT (Box Box 20)
  - 618.19 SCRIP (Box Box 20)
  - 618.131 AMERICAN VECTURIST ASSOCIATION (Box Box 20)
  - APTA NEWS (Box Box 20)
  - RAPID TRANSIT CONFERENCE (Box Box 20)
  - 618.124 OFF BUS SALE OF TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.124 OFF BUS SALE OF TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.131 METAL TOKENS (Box Box 20)
  - 618.123 EXACT FARE (Box Box 20)
  - 618.123 EXACT FARE ATA MATERIAL INQUIRES ETC (Box Box 20)
  - Subway Rail CAsh Transit (Box Box 20)
  - Subway Rail Cash Transit (Box Box 20)
  - URRVS TRAIN CONTROL (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS TRAIN CONTROL (Box Box 21)
  - ACT CONTROLLER (Box Box 21)
  - ACT CONTROLLER (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS COMMUNICATION (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS BRAKES (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS ACT PROGRAM (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS ACT PROGRAM (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS ACT PROGRAM (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS TRUCKS AND SUSPENSION (Box Box 21)
  - ACT - CAB AND BUS (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS 5.3.4. Propulsion (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS 5.3.4. Propulsion (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS 5.3.4. Propulsion (Box Box 21)
  - URRVS 5.3.4. Heating, Ventilating,AC (Box Box 21)
  - 884.265 Surface Cars Subcommittee (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 Questionnaire-Resilient Wheel Pressure Check (Box Box 22)
  - 884.262 Surface Cars Subcommittee (Box Box 22)